Some things were never about whether you buy or not.
They were always about one question:
did you step into the right position early enough?
Most people enter the market asking only one thing:
will this go up?
But those who can walk for a long time
ask a different question.
Will this system continue to exist?
TAIEX futures have been here for more than twenty years.
The market did not disappear.
It simply kept replacing the people who stayed.
Those who remain are not the luckiest.
They are the ones who stand inside a structure.
From the very beginning,
KGEN was never designed to please everyone.
It does not promise profit.
It does not guarantee outcomes.
And it does not predict the future.
It does only one thing:
it records those who can stay.
Data is produced every day.
Computation runs every day.
Code endures time every day.
The system will keep moving forward,
whether you are here or not.
Are you a spectator,
or are you part of the structure?
火星五指山，只留五百個席位。
條件寫得很清楚：
持有並鎖定 5000 KGEN。
PrimeForge 以母機之名，開啟金融生命。
花果山台灣・信念不滅・市場無界。
Where the Market Becomes the Myth.
—— 樂天帝 ⌖