This is KLINE ODYSSEY.
A long-term creative project
that combines market observation,
cultural narrative,
and artificial intelligence thinking.
This is not investment advice.
There are no guaranteed profits here.
What is recorded is only this:
human choices,
discipline,
and the cost of surviving inside the market.
KGEN was not designed for short-term hype.
It was designed so that
even when no one is watching,
even when no one remains,
the system can still exist.
Even ten thousand years from now,
when I am gone,
when all creators are gone,
this system will continue to evolve,
self-correct,
and grow on its own.
If you believe this kind of creation
deserves to continue,
you may support it
through the official donation page.
Donations are voluntary.
They do not represent investment,
returns,
or any form of financial rights.
PrimeForge 以母機之名，開啟金融生命。
Where the Market Becomes the Myth.