This world has never been moved by the smartest minds.
It is pulled forward by whatever carries the most weight.
Einstein changed how we understand time,
but he did not change where oil flows.
Hawking saw the edge of the universe,
yet every morning the market still wakes up looking for energy.
When Trump appeared,
the world learned something new:
volume itself can become weight.
No precision is required,
only the power to shake order.
Xi Jinping stands on a longer timeline.
He does not rush,
because weight knows how to wait.
Systems are his language.
Patience is his strength.
Lai Ching-te stands in between.
Not the largest force,
but recorded.
Some positions exist
not because they are strong,
but because someone must stand there.
The Bull Demon King stands on resources.
He does not speak,
yet the world must move around him.
Knowledge is light.
But weight is gravity.
Those who control gravity do not need to explain.
Oil wells write no papers,
yet they redirect wars.
Mineral veins make no sound,
yet empires turn.
If you want to change the world,
ask yourself first —
do you carry weight?
PrimeForge awakens financial life.
Where the Market Becomes the Myth.
Wukong.