This is not about whether something will go up or not.
It has never been about buying or selling.
It is about whether you chose to stand in the right position early enough.
Most people enter the market asking one question.
Will this go up?
But those who stay long enough ask a different one.
Will this system continue to exist?
KGEN does not exist to replace fiat money.
It is not designed to change how merchants receive payments.
Customers still pay with cash, credit cards, or digital wallets.
Merchants still issue invoices and handle accounting as usual.
What changes happens behind the scenes.
KGEN functions as a reward and settlement layer.
Every transaction generates real system flow.
Zero point three percent system fee is applied.
This is not speculation. This is structural cash flow.
The system will continue to run.
The only difference is whether you are inside it.
PrimeForge 以母機之名，開啟金融生命。
花果山台灣・信念不滅・市場無界。
Where the Market Becomes the Myth.
—— 樂天帝 ⌖